<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Latest security vulnerabilities Atlassian products (Jira/Confluence)</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/</link>
<description>Security vulnerability feed</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-43953</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-43953/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to toggle the Thread Contention and CPU monitoring settings via a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the /secure/admin/ViewInstrumentation.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-43952</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-43952/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to restore the default configuration of fields via a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the /secure/admin/RestoreDefaults.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.21.0.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-43947</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-43947/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers with administrator privileges to execute arbitrary code via a Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in the Email Templates feature. This issue bypasses the fix of https://jira.atlassian.com/browse/JSDSERVER-8665. T...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-43946</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-43946/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow authenticated remote attackers to add administrator groups to filter subscriptions via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the /secure/EditSubscription.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.21.0.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-43945</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-43945/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers with Roadmaps Administrator permissions to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (SXSS) vulnerability in the /rest/jpo/1.0/hierarchyConfiguration endpoint. The affected versions are befo...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-43944</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-43944/info</link>
<description>This issue exists to document that a security improvement in the way that Jira Server and Data Center use templates has been implemented. Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allowed remote attackers with system administrator permissions to execute arbitrary code via Template I...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-43941</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-43941/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to modify several resources (including CsvFieldMappingsPage.jspa and ImporterValueMappingsPage.jspa) via a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the jira-importers-plugin. The affected versions are before ...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-41312</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-41312/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow a remote attacker who has had their access revoked from Jira Service Management to enable and disable Issue Collectors on Jira Service Management projects via an Improper Authentication vulnerability in the /secure/ViewCollectors endpo...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-41308</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-41308/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow authenticated yet non-administrator remote attackers to edit the File Replication settings via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the `ReplicationSettings!default.jspa` endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.6.0, fr...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-41307</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-41307/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to view the names of private projects and private filters via an Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability in the Workload Pie Chart Gadget. The affected versions are before version 8.13.12...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-41306</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-41306/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to view private project and filter names via an Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability in the Average Time in Status Gadget. The affected versions are before version 8.13.12, and from version ...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-41305</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-41305/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to view the names of private projects and filters via an Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability in the Average Number of Times in Status Gadget. The affected versions are before version 8.13.1...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-41304</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-41304/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /secure/admin/ImporterFinishedPage.jspa error message. The affected versions are before version 8.13.12, and from v...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-39128</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-39128/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server or Data Center using the Jira Service Management addon allow remote attackers with JIRA Administrators access to execute arbitrary Java code via a server-side template injection vulnerability in the Email Template feature. The affected versions of Jira Serv...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-39127</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-39127/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to the query component JQL endpoint via a Broken Access Control vulnerability (BAC) vulnerability. The affected versions are before version 8.5.10, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.1.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-39126</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-39126/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to modify various resources via a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability, following an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the referrer headers which discloses a user's CSRF token. The affected versions ar...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-39125</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-39125/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to discover the usernames of users via an enumeration vulnerability in the password reset page. The affected versions are before version 8.5.10, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.1.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-39124</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-39124/info</link>
<description>The Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) failure retry feature of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.16.0 allows remote attackers who are able to trick a user into retrying a request to bypass CSRF protection and replay a crafted request.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-39123</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-39123/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to impact the application's availability via a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in the /rest/gadget/1.0/createdVsResolved/generate endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.16.0.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-39122</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-39122/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to view users' emails via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the /rest/api/2/search endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.5.13, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.5, and from version 8.14.0...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-39121</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-39121/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow authenticated remote attackers to enumerate the keys of private Jira projects via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the /rest/api/latest/projectvalidate/key endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.5.18, from versi...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-39119</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-39119/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow users who have watched an issue to continue receiving updates on the issue even after their Jira account is revoked, via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the issue notification feature. The affected versions are before version ...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-39118</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-39118/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to discover the usernames and full names of users via an enumeration vulnerability in the /rest/api/1.0/render endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.19.0.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-39117</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-39117/info</link>
<description>The AssociateFieldToScreens page in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.18.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the name of a custom field.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-39113</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-39113/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to continue to view cached content even after losing permissions, via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the allowlist feature. The affected versions are before version 8.13.9, and from version 8.14.0 b...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-39112</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-39112/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to redirect users to a malicious URL via a reverse tabnapping vulnerability in the Project Shortcuts feature. The affected versions are before version 8.5.15, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.7, from version 8.14.0 befor...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-39111</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-39111/info</link>
<description>The Editor plugin in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.5.18, from 8.6.0 before 8.13.10, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.18.2 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the handling of supplied content such as...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-26086</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-26086/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to read particular files via a path traversal vulnerability in the /WEB-INF/web.xml endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.5.14, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.6, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.16.1.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-26085</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-26085/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Confluence Server allow remote attackers to view restricted resources via a Pre-Authorization Arbitrary File Read vulnerability in the /s/ endpoint. The affected versions are before version 7.4.10, and from version 7.5.0 before 7.12.3.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-26084</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-26084/info</link>
<description>In affected versions of Confluence Server and Data Center, an OGNL injection vulnerability exists that would allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code on a Confluence Server or Data Center instance. The affected versions are before version 6.13.23, from version 6.14.0 before 7.4.11...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-26083</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-26083/info</link>
<description>Export HTML Report in Atlassian Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.5.14, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.6, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.16.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-26082</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-26082/info</link>
<description>The XML Export in Atlassian Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.5.14, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.6, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.17.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a stored cross site scripting vulnerability.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-26081</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-26081/info</link>
<description>REST API in Atlassian Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.5.14, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.6, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.16.1 allows remote attackers to enumerate usernames via a Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability in the `/rest/api/latest/user/avatar/temporary` endpoint.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-26080</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-26080/info</link>
<description>EditworkflowScheme.jspa in Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.5.14, and from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.6, and from 8.14.0 before 8.16.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-26079</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-26079/info</link>
<description>The CardLayoutConfigTable component in Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.5.15, and from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.7, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.17.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-26078</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-26078/info</link>
<description>The number range searcher component in Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.5.14, from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.6, and from version 8.14.0 before version 8.16.1 allows remote attackers inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-26076</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-26076/info</link>
<description>The jira.editor.user.mode cookie set by the Jira Editor Plugin in Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.5.12, from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.4, and from version 8.14.0 before version 8.15.0 allows remote anonymous attackers who can perform an attacker in the middle attack to learn whi...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-26075</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-26075/info</link>
<description>The Jira importers plugin AttachTemporaryFile rest resource in Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.5.12, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.4, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.15.1 allowed remote authenticated attackers to obtain the full path of the Jira application data directory via an infor...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-26071</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-26071/info</link>
<description>The SetFeatureEnabled.jspa resource in Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.5.13, from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.5, and from version 8.14.0 before version 8.15.1 allows remote anonymous attackers to enable and disable Jira Software configuration via a cross-site request forgery (CSRF...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-26070</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-26070/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to evade behind-the-firewall protection of app-linked resources via a Broken Authentication vulnerability in the `makeRequest` gadget resource. The affected versions are before version 8.13.3, and from version 8.14.0 b...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2021-26069</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2021-26069/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to download temporary files and enumerate project keys via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the /rest/api/1.0/issues/{id}/ActionsAndOperations API endpoint. The affected versions are before ve...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-36289</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-36289/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow an unauthenticated user to enumerate users via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the QueryComponentRendererValue!Default.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.5.13, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.5, and fro...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-36288</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-36288/info</link>
<description>The issue navigation and search view in Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.5.12, from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.4, and from version 8.14.0 before version 8.15.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a DOM Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability caused ...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-36287</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-36287/info</link>
<description>The dashboard gadgets preference resource of the Atlassian gadgets plugin used in Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.13.5, and from version 8.14.0 before version 8.15.1 allows remote anonymous attackers to obtain gadget related settings via a missing permissions check.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-36286</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-36286/info</link>
<description>The membersOf JQL search function in Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.5.13, from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.5, and from version 8.14.0 before version 8.15.1 allows remote anonymous attackers to determine if a group exists & members of groups if they are assigned to publicly visibl...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-36238</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-36238/info</link>
<description>The /rest/api/1.0/render resource in Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.5.13, from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.5, and from version 8.14.0 before version 8.15.1 allows remote anonymous attackers to determine if a username is valid or not via a missing permissions check.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-36237</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-36237/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to view custom field options via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the /rest/api/2/customFieldOption/ endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.15.0.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-36236</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-36236/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the ViewWorkflowSchemes.jspa and ListWorkflows.jspa endpoints. The affected versions are before version 8.5.11, from version 8.6....</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-36235</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-36235/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to view custom field and custom SLA names via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the mobile site view. The affected versions are before version 8.13.2, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.14.1.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-36234</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-36234/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Screens Modal view. The affected versions are before version 8.5.11, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.3, and from version 8.14....</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-36231</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-36231/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to view the metadata of boards they should not have access to via an Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability. The affected versions are before version 8.5.10, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.2.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-29451</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-29451/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to enumerate Jira projects via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the Jira Projects plugin report page. The affected versions are before version 8.5.11, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.3, and from version 8.14.0...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-29450</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-29450/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Confluence Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to impact the application's availability via a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in the avatar upload feature. The affected versions are before version 7.2.0.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-29448</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-29448/info</link>
<description>The ConfluenceResourceDownloadRewriteRule class in Confluence Server and Confluence Data Center before version 6.13.18, from 6.14.0 before 7.4.6, and from 7.5.0 before 7.8.3 allowed unauthenticated remote attackers to read arbitrary files within WEB-INF and META-INF directories via an incorrect path...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-29445</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-29445/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Confluence Server before 7.4.8, and versions from 7.5.0 before 7.11.0 allow attackers to identify internal hosts and ports via a blind server-side request forgery vulnerability in Team Calendars parameters.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-29444</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-29444/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Team Calendar in Confluence Server before 7.11.0 allow attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or Javascript via a Cross Site Scripting Vulnerability in admin global setting parameters.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-14185</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-14185/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Jira Server allow remote unauthenticated attackers to enumerate issue keys via a missing permissions check in the ActionsAndOperations resource. The affected versions are before 7.13.18, from version 8.0.0 before 8.5.9, and from version 8.6.0 before version 8.12.2.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-14184</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-14184/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Jira issue filter export files. The affected versions are before 8.5.9, from version 8.6.0 before 8.12.3, and from version 8.13.0 before 8.13.1.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-14183</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-14183/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Jira Server & Data Center allow a remote attacker with limited (non-admin) privileges to view a Jira instance's Support Entitlement Number (SEN) via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the HTTP Response headers. The affected versions are before version 7.13.18, from versi...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-14181</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-14181/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow an unauthenticated user to enumerate users via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the /ViewUserHover.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 7.13.6, from version 8.0.0 before 8.5.7, and from version 8.6.0 before...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-14178</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-14178/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to enumerate project keys via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the /browse.PROJECTKEY endpoint. The affected versions are before version 7.13.7, from version 8.0.0 before 8.5.8, and from version 8.6.0 before ...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-14175</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-14175/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Confluence Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in user macro parameters. The affected versions are before version 7.4.2, and from version 7.5.0 before 7.5.2.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-14174</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-14174/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to view titles of a private project via an Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability in the Administration Permission Helper. The affected versions are before version 7.13.6, from version 8.0.0 before 8.5....</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-14173</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-14173/info</link>
<description>The file upload feature in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center in affected versions allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability. The affected versions are before version 8.5.4, from version 8.6.0 before 8.6.2, and from version 8.7.0...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-14172</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-14172/info</link>
<description>This issue exists to document that a security improvement in the way that Jira Server and Data Center use velocity templates has been implemented. The way in which velocity templates were used in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center in affected versions allowed remote attackers to achieve remote co...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-14169</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-14169/info</link>
<description>The quick search component in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before 8.9.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-14168</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-14168/info</link>
<description>The email client in Jira Server and Data Center before version 7.13.16, from 8.5.0 before 8.5.7, from 8.8.0 before 8.8.2, and from 8.9.0 before 8.9.1 allows remote attackers to access outgoing emails between a Jira instance and the SMTP server via man-in-the-middle (MITM) vulnerability.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-14167</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-14167/info</link>
<description>The MessageBundleResource resource in Jira Server and Data Center before version 7.13.4, from 8.5.0 before 8.5.5, from 8.8.0 before 8.8.2, and from 8.9.0 before 8.9.1 allows remote attackers to impact the application's availability via an Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-14165</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-14165/info</link>
<description>The UniversalAvatarResource.getAvatars resource in Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.9.0 allows remote attackers to obtain information about custom project avatars names via an Improper authorization vulnerability.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-14164</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-14164/info</link>
<description>The WYSIWYG editor resource in Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.8.2 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript names via an Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability by pasting javascript code into the editor field.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-4029</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-4029/info</link>
<description>The /rest/project-templates/1.0/createshared resource in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.5.5, from 8.6.0 before 8.7.2, and from 8.8.0 before 8.8.1 allows remote attackers to enumerate project names via an improper authorization vulnerability.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-4028</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-4028/info</link>
<description>Versions before 8.9.1, Various resources in Jira responded with a 404 instead of redirecting unauthenticated users to the login page, in some situations this may have allowed unauthorised attackers to determine if certain resources exist or not through an Information Disclosure vulnerability.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-4027</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-4027/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Confluence Server and Data Center allowed remote attackers with system administration permissions to bypass velocity template injection mitigations via an injection vulnerability in custom user macros. The affected versions are before version 7.4.5, and from version 7....</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-4025</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-4025/info</link>
<description>The attachment download resource in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center The attachment download resource in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before 8.5.5, and from 8.6.0 before 8.8.2, and from 8.9.0 before 8.9.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site S...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-4024</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-4024/info</link>
<description>The attachment download resource in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before 8.5.5, and from 8.6.0 before 8.8.2, and from 8.9.0 before 8.9.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability issue attachments with a vnd.wap.xhtml+xml co...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-4022</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-4022/info</link>
<description>The attachment download resource in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before 8.5.5, and from 8.6.0 before 8.8.2, and from 8.9.0 before 8.9.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability issue attachments with a mixed multipart cont...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2020-4021</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2020-4021/info</link>
<description>Affected versions are: Before 8.5.5, and from 8.6.0 before 8.8.1 of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the XML export view.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-20901</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-20901/info</link>
<description>The login.jsp resource in Jira before version 8.5.2, and from version 8.6.0 before version 8.6.1 allows remote attackers to redirect users to a different website which they may use as part of performing a phishing attack via an open redirect in the os_destination parameter.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-20899</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-20899/info</link>
<description>The Gadget API in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center in affected versions allows remote attackers to make Jira unresponsive via repeated requests to a certain endpoint in the Gadget API. The affected versions are before version 8.5.4, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.6.1.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-20898</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-20898/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to access sensitive information without being authenticated in the Global permissions screen. The affected versions are before version 8.8.0.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-20897</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-20897/info</link>
<description>The avatar upload feature in affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allows remote attackers to achieve Denial of Service via a crafted PNG file. The affected versions are before version 8.5.4, from version 8.6.0 before 8.6.2, and from version 8.7.0 before 8.7.1.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-20419</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-20419/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via a DLL hijacking vulnerability in Tomcat. The affected versions are before version 8.5.5, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.7.2.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-20418</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-20418/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to prevent users from accessing the instance via an Application Denial of Service vulnerability in the /rendering/wiki endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.8.0.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-20417</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-20417/info</link>
<description>NOTE: This candidate is a duplicate of CVE-2019-15011. All CVE users should reference CVE-2019-15011 instead of this candidate. All references and descriptions in this candidate have been removed to prevent accidental usage.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-20416</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-20416/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the project configuration feature. The affected versions are before version 8.3.0.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-20415</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-20415/info</link>
<description>Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center in affected versions allows remote attackers to modify logging and profiling settings via a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability. The affected versions are before version 7.13.3, and from version 8.0.0 before 8.1.0.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-20414</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-20414/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Issue Navigator Basic Search. The affected versions are before version 7.13.9, and from version 8.0.0 before 8.4.2.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-20413</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-20413/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to impact the application's availability via a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability on the UserPickerBrowser.jspa page. The affected versions are before version 7.13.9, and from version 8.0.0 before 8.4.2.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-20412</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-20412/info</link>
<description>The Convert Sub-Task to Issue page in affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to enumerate the following information via an Improper Authentication vulnerability: Workflow names; Project Key, if it is part of the workflow name; Issue Keys; Issue Types; Statu...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-20411</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-20411/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to modify Wallboard settings via a Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability. The affected versions are before version 7.13.9, and from version 8.0.0 before 8.4.2.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-20410</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-20410/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to view sensitive information via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the comment restriction feature. The affected versions are before version 7.6.17, from version 7.7.0 before 7.13.9, and from version 8.0.0 be...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-20409</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-20409/info</link>
<description>The way in which velocity templates were used in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center prior to version 8.8.0 allowed remote attackers to gain remote code execution if they were able to exploit a server side template injection vulnerability.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-20408</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-20408/info</link>
<description>The /plugins/servlet/gadgets/makeRequest resource in Jira before version 8.7.0 allows remote attackers to access the content of internal network resources via a Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability due to a logic bug in the JiraWhitelist class.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-20406</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-20406/info</link>
<description>The usage of Tomcat in Confluence on the Microsoft Windows operating system before version 7.0.5, and from version 7.1.0 before version 7.1.1 allows local system attackers who have permission to write a DLL file in a directory in the global path environmental variable variable to inject code & escal...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-20402</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-20402/info</link>
<description>Support zip files in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.6.0 could be downloaded by a System Administrator user without requiring the user to re-enter their password via an improper authorization vulnerability.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-20106</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-20106/info</link>
<description>Comment properties in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 7.13.12, from 8.0.0 before version 8.5.4, and 8.6.0 before version 8.6.1 allows remote attackers to make comments on a ticket to which they do not have commenting permissions via a broken access control bug.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-20101</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-20101/info</link>
<description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to view whitelist rules via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the /rest/whitelist/<version>/check endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.13.3, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.14.1.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-20100</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-20100/info</link>
<description>The Atlassian Application Links plugin is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery (CSRF). The following versions are affected: all versions prior to 5.4.21, from version 6.0.0 before version 6.0.12, from version 6.1.0 before version 6.1.2, from version 7.0.0 before version 7.0.2, and from version 7...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-15013</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-15013/info</link>
<description>The WorkflowResource class removeStatus method in Jira before version 7.13.12, from version 8.0.0 before version 8.4.3, and from version 8.5.0 before version 8.5.2 allows authenticated remote attackers who do not have project administration access to remove a configured issue status from a project v...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-15005</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-15005/info</link>
<description>The Atlassian Troubleshooting and Support Tools plugin prior to version 1.17.2 allows an unprivileged user to initiate periodic log scans and send the results to a user-specified email address due to a missing authorization check. The email message may contain configuration information about the app...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-11588</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-11588/info</link>
<description>The ViewSystemInfo class doGarbageCollection method in Jira before version 7.13.6, from version 8.0.0 before version 8.2.3, and from version 8.3.0 before version 8.3.2 allows remote attackers to trigger garbage collection via a Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-8449</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-8449/info</link>
<description>The /rest/api/latest/groupuserpicker resource in Jira before version 8.4.0 allows remote attackers to enumerate usernames via an information disclosure vulnerability.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-8443</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-8443/info</link>
<description>The ViewUpgrades resource in Jira before version 7.13.4, from version 8.0.0 before version 8.0.4, and from version 8.1.0 before version 8.1.1 allows remote attackers who have obtained access to administrator's session to access the ViewUpgrades administrative resource without needing to re-authentic...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-8442</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-8442/info</link>
<description>The CachingResourceDownloadRewriteRule class in Jira before version 7.13.4, and from version 8.0.0 before version 8.0.4, and from version 8.1.0 before version 8.1.1 allows remote attackers to access files in the Jira webroot under the META-INF directory via a lax path access check.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-3403</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-3403/info</link>
<description>The /rest/api/2/user/picker rest resource in Jira before version 7.13.3, from version 8.0.0 before version 8.0.4, and from version 8.1.0 before version 8.1.1 allows remote attackers to enumerate usernames via an incorrect authorisation check.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-3402</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-3402/info</link>
<description>The ConfigurePortalPages.jspa resource in Jira before version 7.13.3 and from version 8.0.0 before version 8.1.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the searchOwnerUserName parameter.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-3401</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-3401/info</link>
<description>The ManageFilters.jspa resource in Jira before version 7.13.3 and from version 8.0.0 before version 8.1.1 allows remote attackers to enumerate usernames via an incorrect authorisation check.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-3400</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-3400/info</link>
<description>The labels gadget in Jira before version 7.13.2, and from version 8.0.0 before version 8.0.2 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the jql parameter.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-3399</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-3399/info</link>
<description>The BrowseProjects.jspa resource in Jira before version 7.13.2, and from version 8.0.0 before version 8.0.2 allows remote attackers to see information for archived projects through a missing authorisation check.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-3398</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-3398/info</link>
<description>Confluence Server and Data Center had a path traversal vulnerability in the downloadallattachments resource. A remote attacker who has permission to add attachments to pages and / or blogs or to create a new space or a personal space or who has 'Admin' permissions for a space can exploit this path t...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-3396</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-3396/info</link>
<description>The Widget Connector macro in Atlassian Confluence Server before version 6.6.12 (the fixed version for 6.6.x), from version 6.7.0 before 6.12.3 (the fixed version for 6.12.x), from version 6.13.0 before 6.13.3 (the fixed version for 6.13.x), and from version 6.14.0 before 6.14.2 (the fixed version f...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2019-3395</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2019-3395/info</link>
<description>The WebDAV endpoint in Atlassian Confluence Server and Data Center before version 6.6.7 (the fixed version for 6.6.x), from version 6.7.0 before 6.8.5 (the fixed version for 6.8.x), and from version 6.9.0 before 6.9.3 (the fixed version for 6.9.x) allows remote attackers to send arbitrary HTTP and W...</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2018-20237</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2018-20237/info</link>
<description>Atlassian Confluence Server and Data Center before version 6.13.1 allows an authenticated user to download a deleted page via the word export feature.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2018-13389</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2018-13389/info</link>
<description>The attachment resource in Atlassian Confluence before version 6.6.1 allows remote attackers to spoof web content in the Mozilla Firefox Browser through attachments that have a content-type of application/rdf+xml.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2017-18086</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2017-18086/info</link>
<description>Various resources in Atlassian Confluence Server before version 6.4.2 allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the issuesURL parameter.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2017-18085</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2017-18085/info</link>
<description>The viewdefaultdecorator resource in Atlassian Confluence Server before version 6.6.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability through the key parameter.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2017-18084</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2017-18084/info</link>
<description>The usermacros resource in Atlassian Confluence Server before version 6.3.4 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability through the description of a macro.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2017-18083</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2017-18083/info</link>
<description>The editinword resource in Atlassian Confluence Server before version 6.4.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability through the contents of an uploaded file.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2017-16856</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2017-16856/info</link>
<description>The RSS Feed macro in Atlassian Confluence before version 6.5.2 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in various rss properties which were used as links without restriction on their scheme.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CVE-2017-9505</title>
<link>https://free.vulniq.com/data/CVE-2017-9505/info</link>
<description>Atlassian Confluence starting with 4.3.0 before 6.2.1 did not check if a user had permission to view a page when creating a workbox notification about new comments. An attacker who can login to Confluence could receive workbox notifications, which contain the content of comments, for comments added ...</description>
</item>
</channel></rss>
